malabargoldanddiamonds.com 2018-09-13

# Privacy Policy | Malabar Gold & Diamonds

We know that you trust malabargoldanddiamonds.com. This is the reason we have set high standards for our secured transactions and adherence to the customer information privacy. Please note that our privacy policy will be subject to changes at any point in time without any prior notice.

### WE REQUEST YOU TO REFER THE BELOW TERMS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY

##### PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT ARE COLLECTED

We usually collect personal information like name, email id, contact number and such other details during the process of setting up an account with malabargoldanddiamonds.com. When browsing a few sections of site without you being a registered member, you will not be able to place an order. We use your contact details so that we can intimate you about the timely offers, which are based on the previous orders and also depends on your interest.

##### USE OF INFORMATION

We make use of the personal details for providing you with service requests. For various purposes like troubleshooting problems, collection of fees, for surveys and for providing information on various offers, we need your personal information. We also collect and analyze the demographic and profile data about users activity in our website. We make sure to identify and use the IP address for diagnosing problems in our website.

##### SECURITY PRECAUTIONS

Our site is featured with strict security measures and due to this, we help in protecting the loss, alteration and misuse of information under our control. If in case you want to change your access of personal account information, we make sure to provide with secure server. Once the information is with us, we make sure to adhere to the stringent security guidelines and protect the same against unauthorized access.

##### CHOICE/OPT-OUT

malabargoldanddiamonds.com provides to all the users with a chance of opting out of promotional and marketing related services from us on behalf of our partners, after you set up an account.
